[{"answer": "No, he did not.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 30, "question": "Did Dr. Murray ever mention to you having administered Propofol to Michael Jackson?", "qSentId": 29}, {"answer": "No, he did not.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 32, "question": "Did Conrad Murray ever mention the word Propofol to you during the time that you were at the location or in his presence?", "qSentId": 31}, {"answer": "I haven't seen any of the trial.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 53, "question": "What would he make of all this?", "qSentId": 52}, {"answer": "I'm more damaged -- I feel more damaged now than I ever remember feeling as a child.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 85, "question": "I mean, notwithstanding that, do you still feel slightly damaged by the whole process of stardom for so long?", "qSentId": 84}, {"answer": "Because I was a kid, and I also had a lot of fun, and a lot of opportunity.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 87, "question": "Really, why?", "qSentId": 86}, {"answer": "Because I'm -- because in a way, I was so protected, and I was so naive, I was sort of -- I maintained a level of naivete for so long that now when I see things, the way the business is, the way the industry is, the way the world is, I'm so much more affected by it, because I can't believe -- I always say I hate people, you know, because I'm not -- I did not get hardened by it.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 94, "question": "Why do you feel damaged now?", "qSentId": 93}, {"answer": "I think -- we talked about it a little bit.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 98, "question": "Is this very similar, do you think, to the way Michael Jackson probably felt?", "qSentId": 97}, {"answer": "I pray to God that they don't want to.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 105, "question": "How do you feel about your own children going into any sort of fame?", "qSentId": 104}, {"answer": "Listening.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 128, "question": "What are you doing?", "qSentId": 127}, {"answer": "It's devastating.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 140, "question": "What do you make of what's happening to your country in terms of so many people now out of work, suffering financial problems?", "qSentId": 139}, {"answer": "I am.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 146, "question": "Are you a fan of President Obama?", "qSentId": 145}, {"answer": "Thank you.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 156, "question": "When, in fact, you got a great brain?", "qSentId": 155}, {"answer": "Here's the thing.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 167, "question": "Should it matter?", "qSentId": 166}, {"answer": "Beer, next.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 221, "question": "Coming up -- sorry?", "qSentId": 220}, {"answer": "Not now, I want one from your pub.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 223, "question": "You want a beer?", "qSentId": 222}, {"answer": "Incredibly warm and happy memories for me.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 255, "question": "Horrible memories?", "qSentId": 254}, {"answer": "I was pretty good, yes.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 269, "question": "But you were good?", "qSentId": 268}, {"answer": "I was a good catcher.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 272, "question": "You were a hot athlete in your day?", "qSentId": 271}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 281, "question": "Not true?", "qSentId": 280}, {"answer": "I don't like or dislike it.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 300, "question": "Do you like the fact that you have this slightly intimidating reputation?", "qSentId": 299}, {"answer": "I think America needs lots of tough people.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 329, "question": "Do you think America needs somebody like you who's going to be tough?", "qSentId": 328}, {"answer": "I think if -- the best quality she would say is brutally honest, tough, and compassionate.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 352, "question": "If you were being honest, what do you think your mother would have said were your best qualities, and what would she say would be your not-so-good qualities?", "qSentId": 351}, {"answer": "Yes, you can.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 357, "question": "Can we hold you to that, Governor?", "qSentId": 356}, {"answer": "Well, listen, my wife didn't like the jokes.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 359, "question": "Is that one of those little jokes where you think, hang on, maybe I went too far there?", "qSentId": 358}, {"answer": "Because that's not the way you make decisions like running for president of the United States.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 376, "question": "Why wouldn't you?", "qSentId": 375}, {"answer": "Listen, I've been governor for --", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 381, "question": "ORGAN: Why aren't you ready?", "qSentId": 380}, {"answer": "I'm 48.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 383, "question": "How old are you now?", "qSentId": 382}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 397, "question": "You're a straight talker, right?", "qSentId": 396}, {"answer": "You're wrong.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 405, "question": "Can you?", "qSentId": 404}, {"answer": "There are so many variables to that, Piers.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 411, "question": "Are you 100 percent certain you won't run in 2016?", "qSentId": 410}, {"answer": "Senior class, junior class, sophomore class -- yes, all the way through.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 419, "question": "You were always a bit of a high flyer here -- president of everything, right?", "qSentId": 418}, {"answer": "HRISTIE: Well, I think that you have to understand that we are not a religious democracy.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 442, "question": "Can you divorce being a Catholic with all that that means and all you stand for as a Catholic -- and I'm a Catholic -- from running for high office?", "qSentId": 441}, {"answer": "Well, my religion says it's a sin.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 453, "question": "Is homosexuality a sin?", "qSentId": 452}, {"answer": "I don't think so.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 460, "question": "Can you see a situation where you would change your mind about that?", "qSentId": 459}, {"answer": "You don't look like a priest to me, Piers.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 496, "question": "Obviously in light of Weiner-gate, Schwarzenegger-gate, and so on, is there anything you want to get off your chest?", "qSentId": 495}, {"answer": "You know, listen, any confessions I need to make, I'll make to my wife and to my priest, not on CNN to you, pal.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 499, "question": "Well, should we be ever worried about any skeletons tumbling out of the Christie closet?", "qSentId": 498}, {"answer": "Listen, I had a Sicilian mother.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 502, "question": "Do you ever feel guilty about stuff?", "qSentId": 501}, {"answer": "It depends on the day.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 505, "question": "What do you feel most guilty about?", "qSentId": 504}, {"answer": "Yes, because I'm really struggling, been struggling for a long time with it.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 508, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 507}, {"answer": "If I could figure it out, I'd fix it.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 512, "question": "Why do you think you've had a battle with your weight?", "qSentId": 511}, {"answer": "I don't.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 514, "question": "You don't know what it is?", "qSentId": 513}, {"answer": "Sure, plenty of times.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 516, "question": "Do you ever get help for it?", "qSentId": 515}, {"answer": "I eat too much.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 518, "question": "Where do you fall down in terms of dealing with it?", "qSentId": 517}, {"answer": "HRISTIE: No.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 522, "question": "Is it -- is it the one jibe about you that really stings?", "qSentId": 521}, {"answer": "You know, my wife was asked this question and she said yes.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 532, "question": "Final question for here, do you think you would make a good president?", "qSentId": 531}, {"answer": "A lot, especially when I was running for office.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 540, "question": "How much of your life have you spent in places like this?", "qSentId": 539}, {"answer": "It was a place to socialize for teenagers, a place where we could come.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 547, "question": "Other than nice food and coffee?", "qSentId": 546}, {"answer": "It's OK.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 559, "question": "How do you feel about that?", "qSentId": 558}, {"answer": "I think it is.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 561, "question": "Is that the New Jersey way?", "qSentId": 560}, {"answer": "You know, it's -- we're still evaluating you, Piers.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 591, "question": "Why are you looking at me that way?", "qSentId": 590}, {"answer": "No, I think we're more of a team than one person wearing the trousers.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 626, "question": "Is that an accurate description?", "qSentId": 625}, {"answer": "I definitely think I'm a good woman.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 629, "question": "Do you go along with that?", "qSentId": 628}, {"answer": "Yes, I'd agree with that.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 640, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 639}, {"answer": "Well, I'm sure his country could use him but his family needs him too.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 644, "question": "What if your country needs him?", "qSentId": 643}, {"answer": "Because Chris has an -- an unbelievable ability to succinctly analyze a problem, come up with solutions, listen to people and then communicate the solutions.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 657, "question": "What is it about him, do you think, that if it came to it, if it came to a presidential race, why should Americans vote for him?", "qSentId": 656}, {"answer": "No, not at all.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 666, "question": "Anything you want to share with us?", "qSentId": 665}, {"answer": "Probably that he's mean.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 670, "question": "What's the single biggest misconception about your husband, do you think?", "qSentId": 669}, {"answer": "But he's a really good person.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 673, "question": "He's the nicest, most ferocious prosecutor you've ever met, right?", "qSentId": 672}, {"answer": "Well, I don't know about that.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 677, "question": "Bit of a pussycat really?", "qSentId": 676}, {"answer": "You're putting words into my mouth, Piers.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 679, "question": "Wouldn't go that far?", "qSentId": 678}, {"answer": "No, I mean, I -- I really was just happy that he coming to the game.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 691, "question": "How did you feel?", "qSentId": 690}, {"answer": "Maybe -- maybe it was a good intimidation tactic.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 703, "question": "Now, are you happy if that helicopter comes into sight again in the middle of the game?", "qSentId": 702}, {"answer": "Seventeen.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 706, "question": "Well, you are at an age -- how old are you now?", "qSentId": 705}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 710, "question": "When you look -- are you a Republican by nature, would you say?", "qSentId": 709}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I -- I guess part of me thinks that, a little bit, but I -- I don't think for us personally as a family and for him it would be the best idea.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 712, "question": "When you look at the other candidates doesn't part of you think, wow, wish the old man would run, because he'd have a better chance?", "qSentId": 711}, {"answer": "Because I ask him that all the time too.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 730, "question": "When he says that, he means it?", "qSentId": 729}, {"answer": "Well, I just want to be sure, because I just don't want him to.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 733, "question": "Why would you keep having to ask him if -- if when he says it, you believe him?", "qSentId": 732}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 740, "question": "Would you like him to?", "qSentId": 739}, {"answer": "I just want him to be healthy.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 746, "question": "Sarah, why are you concerned about it?", "qSentId": 745}, {"answer": "The best things.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 753, "question": "Finally, you two, what would you say are the best things about your dad and the most annoying?", "qSentId": 752}, {"answer": "He told me that -- in the campaign, I'd asked if I was going to have to have state police with me all the time.", "docId": "110930pmt", "aSentId": 762, "question": "I'll bet he's a nightmare isn't he?", "qSentId": 761}]